<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Adam Whitlock</title>
    <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Adam Whitlock</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamwhitlock.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microphone Settings for Zoom</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/zoom-microphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/zoom-microphone/</guid>
      <description>How I sound shouldn’t be a distraction if I’m talking with my colleagues on Zoom. I use a variety of microphones during the day. Built-in MacBook Pro, AirPods, and my trusty Shure SM7B dynamic microphone. Each microphone has its own sound and purpose. Sometimes it’s for high quality recordings or interviews, while other times for ease. Microphones are not the only variable, since location changes too. My team can tell you I call from coffee shops a number of times, which can be noisy depending on who ordered an espresso. My home office/bedroom doesn’t have much on the walls or floor, making it perfect for echoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Humans Troubleshoot</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/humans-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/humans-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>“Cognitive load” is a term that refers to the amount of working memory resources someone can process at a given time. Working memory is a limited resource in capacity, related to how we learn and process information. If we have a lot of distractions (noise) or are constantly shifting tasks, it can impact our ability to learn. Why does this matter? During troubleshooting, people are actively trying to learn about what is happening in a system. They need to gather facts and understand what happened. Decisions need to be made. Depending on incident severity, the pressure to get things working can also be strong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikes</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/bicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/bicycle/</guid>
      <description>Bicycling I&amp;rsquo;m not the big cyclist, where I join races or need to keep up on the Tour de France.
Bicycles All City Mr. Pink A steel-frame bicycle is what I think about when I think about bicycles. I wanted something that looked “classic” yet was very modern in components and feel. All City makes great frames, with the Mr. Pink being a now-discontinued racing frame. It’s my understanding they make a similar frame, but with different steel. This Mr. Pink has Columbus Zona tubes, with interior routing for cabling. This makes it easier to maintain and keep cabling mishaps from happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo, through Design</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</guid>
      <description>I would play with site design every day, from when I got home from work until passing out after 2AM. My workspace was a corner desk with a large 22&amp;quot; flat screen CRT and a Mac mini, with barely enough memory to drive the display. My chair constantly hit the railing of my bed, which barely fit in the room. The screen made it feel like the room was bigger. What I worked on made it feel like anything was good enough.
People used what I made and that was rewarding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Coffee Snob No, not really. I&amp;rsquo;ve lived off of vending machine coffee. There are break rooms and rest stops where I know what number pad combination makes me a coffee I&amp;rsquo;ll drink for the next hour. Gas stations can make a decent brew, necessary when driving across the country.
I might come across as a coffee snob because I care a lot about roasts and equipment. OK, I can accept that. However, just because I spend money on coffee doesn&amp;rsquo;t immediately make me a snob. I choose to spend more money than most people, which is fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Information</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you want to personally reach out to me, please send an email to &amp;ldquo;adam [at] adamwhitlock [dot] com&amp;rdquo;. I don&amp;rsquo;t check my email daily, unless I&amp;rsquo;m expecting something, so please wait a day or two before sending a followup message. Additionally, check out my social media profiles below.
 LinkedIn Github Twitter  If this is concerning something professional, like a business opportunity, please reach out using LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s This About</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Adam Whitlock (pronouns he/him) and I like to think of myself as being many things.
Professional Work Engineering Management I keep an updated manager README.md on Github if you want to learn how I approach management and my guiding principles.
Site Design &amp;amp; Details The site is hosted on Github, using Github Pages. Website code is statically generated, meaning that all content on this site was pre-generated and not rendered. There&amp;rsquo;s no Javascript in use at the moment, but if some gets added I&amp;rsquo;ll hopefully remember to update this section with that info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Streaming with Volumio and Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</guid>
      <description>I wanted a device that could stream audio from a media server like Plex, not be reliant on Bluetooth for connectivity, allow me to use my existing speakers, and provide high quality audio output. I also wanted a solution that didn’t have me vendor-locked, like using Chromecast Audio or Amazon Echo. This left little options, other than buying a very nice wireless DAC or similar device.
About nine months ago it occurred to me that I could build what I wanted, far cheaper than most solutions. It would also prove to be a fun project and stretch some of my knowledge of audiophile equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
