<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Adam Whitlock</title>
    <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Adam Whitlock</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamwhitlock.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hugo through Design</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</guid>
      <description>I used to play with site design every day, from when I got home from work until I passed out at 2 in the morning. I&amp;rsquo;d feel motivated to make some element splash onto the DOM for the first time, seeing how it worked. Twiddling away at design was fun, but after a while I lost my motivation for it. I know why and I know which browser to blame (Internet Explorer), but hadn&amp;rsquo;t really jumped back into it. I have done some light design work for jobs, but mostly to get tools working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Coffee Equipment Here&amp;rsquo;s a listing of coffee equipment I use for various methods
Equipment for pour-over
 Kalita &amp;ldquo;Wave&amp;rdquo; #185 coffee dripper Acaia Pearl Model S scale Hario Coffee Server, 600ml Fellow Ode Brew coffee grinder  Coffee Roasters Approved Roasters (United States)
 Ruby Coffee Roasters Verve Coffee Roasters Chromatic Coffee Company Wrecking Ball Coffee Roasters Tandem Coffee Roasters Cat &amp;amp; Cloud Coffee Brandywine Coffee Roasters Wonderstate Coffee Roasters Black and White Coffee Roasters Isley Coffee Roasters *Onyx Coffee Lab Handlebar Coffee Roasters Johnson Brothers Coffee (JBC) Bird Rock *Counter Culture Heart Roasters Temple Coffee Roasters Pair Cupworks Dune Coffee Roasters Hey Coffee Company Camber Coffee Corvus Roasters Sweet Bloom Red Rooster Coffee *Equator Coffee Spectrum Coffees  *Roasters with an asterisk are considered by Adam Whitlock to be too popular for their own good, which can impact consistency</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Information</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you want to personally reach out to me, please send an email to &amp;ldquo;adam [at] adamwhitlock [dot] com&amp;rdquo;. I don&amp;rsquo;t check my email daily, unless I&amp;rsquo;m expecting something, so please wait a day or two before sending a followup message. Additionally, check out my social media profiles below.
 LinkedIn Github Twitter  If this is concerning something professional, like a business opportunity, please reach out using LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s This About</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Adam Whitlock (pronouns he/him) and do things.
Professional I&amp;rsquo;m an engineering manager, former sysadmin, and other things.
Personal I&amp;rsquo;ve got a personal life. Fill this out.
Site Design &amp;amp; Details The site is hosted on Github, using Github Pages. Website code is statically generated, meaning that all content on this site was pre-generated and not rendered. There&amp;rsquo;s no Javascript in use at the moment, but if some gets added I&amp;rsquo;ll hopefully remember to update this section with that info. I use Hugo, which is a static site generation framework written in Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Streaming with Volumio and Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</guid>
      <description>I wanted a device that could stream audio from a media server like Plex, not be reliant on Bluetooth for connectivity, allow me to use my existing speakers, and provide high quality audio output. I also wanted a solution that didn’t have me vendor-locked, like using Chromecast Audio or Amazon Echo. This left little options, other than buying a very nice wireless DAC or similar device.
About nine months ago it occurred to me that I could build what I wanted, far cheaper than most solutions. It would also prove to be a fun project and stretch some of my knowledge of audiophile equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
