<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archive on Adam Whitlock</title>
    <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archive on Adam Whitlock</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:31:55 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hugo through Design</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/hugo-design/</guid>
      <description>I used to play with site design every day, from when I got home from work until I passed out at 2 in the morning. I&amp;rsquo;d feel motivated to make some element splash onto the DOM for the first time, seeing how it worked. Twiddling away at design was fun, but after a while I lost my motivation for it. I know why and I know which browser to blame (Internet Explorer), but hadn&amp;rsquo;t really jumped back into it. I have done some light design work for jobs, but mostly to get tools working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Streaming with Volumio and Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamwhitlock.com/archive/volumio/</guid>
      <description>I wanted a device that could stream audio from a media server like Plex, not be reliant on Bluetooth for connectivity, allow me to use my existing speakers, and provide high quality audio output. I also wanted a solution that didn’t have me vendor-locked, like using Chromecast Audio or Amazon Echo. This left little options, other than buying a very nice wireless DAC or similar device.
About nine months ago it occurred to me that I could build what I wanted, far cheaper than most solutions. It would also prove to be a fun project and stretch some of my knowledge of audiophile equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
